Hello everyone
I'm Coach Xiao Hui, your AI trainer
Today, we'll carry on with
Chapter Three, Section One
Hello
Everyone
I'm Coach Xiao Hui, your AI trainer
Today, we'll continue with Chapter Three, Section Two
the operation of Douyin accounts
First, before we start,
we're going to cover some knowledge about TikTok operations,
which is closely related to our course content.
We'll focus on the parts that are most relevant.
These are the basics of account management.
Of course,
these principles are quite universal and generally applicable.
They form the foundational logic.
Of course,
Mainly, it's about the foundational knowledge of operations related to the projects we'll be working on later.
This includes some basic operational knowledge that's quite relevant.
The content here is not differentiated by format,
Are you a posts or a short video?
It's all quite universal.
Everything can be applied across the board.
The same principles apply when you create other types of content as well.
However, we can't cover everything in detail today,
since this isn't a comprehensive course on Douyin.
So, we'll be combining what we plan to do next,
some AI painting projects,
Or some of the short video projects, right?
to give you an overview of the basics.
It mainly consists of seven parts,
and I'll expand on these seven aspects.
The first part is about setting up our account.
The second part is about account positioning.
The third part is about Douyin's traffic algorithm.
So, let's create a Douyin account.
The first two are the fundamentals, right?
You need to package your account well first.
You need traffic, right?
Before we work on the traffic,
we need to understand Douyin's
underlying traffic algorithm.
The fourth part is about content creation techniques.
The fifth part is about operation techniques.
Now that we've covered the basics
we're ready
we need to create content, right?
to gain followers and monetize through that content
the sixth point is about methods for attracting traffic and monetizing
the seventh is about Douyin's rules
when we're managing our accounts
since we rely on the platform, right?
we definitely need to follow the platform's rules
Alright, let's get started.
Let's talk about the first part.
We'll start with setting up a Douyin account.
First, before we create an account, you need to have one, right?
When registering, we should aim for one phone, one SIM, one account.
What do you mean?
I mean, one phone.
One SIM card.
For one Douyin account.
And when you register, don't use this WiFi.
Try to use 4G or 5G networks instead.
If you're with one carrier,
you can have five accounts, you know.
So one ID can open five accounts.
With the three major carriers,
you could potentially have 15 accounts.
15 SIM cards can register 15 Douyin accounts.
Once you've completed the registration,
There's no need to rush
to complete the real-name verification immediately
You can do the verification when you need it
For example, when you want to activate a service window or start a live stream,
That's when you should do the verification
You can still post content without real-name verification
The second step, after registering your account
is to engage in some account nurturing activities
This account nurturing thing, some people say it's like a metaphysical concept from Douyin's official side.
He said it doesn't need quotation marks.
But we think
to avoid affecting the account's traffic
or when it can be activated
it might be labeled as a marketing account
we believe the process of nurturing the account is necessary.
It's actually not very complicated.
Basically, it just requires
a 3 to 5 day or 5 to 7 day process.
This process is mainly about
imitating a regular user on Douyin
and here I've listed
a 5 to 7-day account nurturing process
On your first day, you should follow the accounts of influential figures in your field.
what does 'in your niche' mean?
it means the type of account you're creating
an account in the same category
for example, if you're creating a comedy account
Then go and follow some funny big V accounts.
For example, if you want to create a relationship channel,
Then you should follow some influential figures in the realm of emotions.
The next day, spend an hour in the morning, afternoon, and evening,
scrolling through similar tags.
This will help tag your account with interest categories.
What are interest tags?
Once you have your own interests,
Then TikTok will recommend content for you.
videos related to the recommended tags
For example, if you like watching comedy videos, right?
TikTok will recommend funny videos to you.
Or if you also enjoy this kind of thing
Binge-watching dramas and such, right?
He will recommend some film and TV accounts to you.
In the evening, we can go around the city together
Check out the live streams of your peers
Spend about half an hour to an hour
Leave a few comments and that’s it.
On days 3 to 5, repeat what you did in the first two days.
After you've completed the account nurturing process,
go ahead and update your profile and bio.
There are two signs that you've successfully nurtured your account:
It will recommend a large amount of
accounts similar to yours,
and your interests will have been established as the second sign,
you'll also come across some low-quality content.
This one usually gets dozens of likes.
They might be your peers who just posted it.
Some that were just released.
Works that are still in the initial traffic pool.
The second part is about our account's positioning.
This positioning,
for our account,
lays the foundation for our account.
What is its positioning?
When we talk about creating an account, we need to focus on a specific niche, right?
So, our account will also have a presence on Douyin,
and it will help to tag our account with a specific niche.
For the same account,
we should try to produce content within the same niche.
Instead of doing everything under the sun,
trying to cover relationships,
as well as comedy,
and even film and TV.
What kind of product promotion are we doing?
Then the account tags will become quite messy on Douyin.
So, it won’t be able to match the right audience for your account.
More precise traffic.
So, first, we need to clearly define our account.
Get a good positioning.
How do you position yourself in your content?
First, you need to understand yourself.
For example, if you are running an IP account.
Right?
Then you need to be the one to appear on camera.
So you need to recognize your own strengths.
Your learning ability,
and your vision,
what you want to do,
what you want your account to look like.
For example, I want to do this short video for product promotion, right?
Then you should specialize in creating content for product sales.
The other content isn't yours, though.
The main focus should be on what you're planning to release.
Following the monetization path and niche areas we planned before,
identify ten
top accounts in your field.
This process is called finding benchmark accounts.
You need to find ten benchmark accounts.
I mean, what you want to achieve,
what kind of content you want to create.
Find accounts that are similar to yours
Look for ones that are about the same level as you
Study them
Analyze their hit content
Examine their data
and then use the recommendations we provide later
Some of the data query tools
I've recommended this to you before.
Like Chan Mama
or archaeologists, and so on
and then look up a certain account
Specifically, the public opinion of his followers
What is fan sentiment?
what aspect of his, you know
You should really pay more attention to user comments.
What's the point of his comment?
we need to analyze these points
then put yourself in their shoes
Conduct a simulation exercise
and you'll know what kind of content you want to post
The second step is to establish the basic elements of your persona
First, you need to analyze who you are
We can use the SWOT analysis method
which is a way to analyze
your strengths and weaknesses, and so on
what you want to achieve
what the content of your account will be
What is your personal brand positioning?
In other words, what perception do you want people to have of you?
So, what value can you bring to your followers?
Find your own strengths and the value you can bring to your followers.
Once you have a clear understanding of these aspects of your positioning,
You can start setting up your profile now.
This includes the nickname for your Douyin account,
profile picture, and bio, among others.
We all know the importance of a name.
He is indeed very important.
The first impression starts with our name.
A good name.
A good name can convey your vision and expectations.
And it's also easier to spread.
Choosing a name that's easy to remember is key.
That makes it a good name.
Here, we've listed three criteria for you.
Three criteria for a good name.
First, it’s memorable.
Others can easily remember your name.
Second, it’s comprehensible.
Just by seeing your account name,
they know what you do.
Third, it must be easy to spread.
When your name is mentioned,
relevant words come to mind.
No need for further explanation.
There's no need to go through other means.
This will leave an impression in the user's mind.
Now, let me give you a few examples of accounts.
For instance, if you're creating a niche account.
For example, if you need to target a specific audience.
Besides creating content for Douyin.
Apart from building a personal brand.
It's more about preparing for future sales.
Or making money from ads.
So, attracting a specific audience is pretty crucial.
For example, our renovation team clearly looks like they're in the renovation business.
Right?
Lifestyle aestheticians
They obviously work in aesthetics or art-related fields.
These are professional nicknames that reflect their careers.
Including their profession, of course.
Add some personalized terms.
To make users feel connected.
This account is a real person, you know.
For example, the seasoned copywriter Tang Xiaotian has posted this copy.
Obviously, they are in the copywriting field, right?
The second one is named Courier Extraordinaire.
Wu Yanzu.
It’s clear that they are in the courier business.
There’s no need to explain this one.
It’s pretty straightforward.
More vertical
It's called graphic design
The third type
This is the opinion leader type
So when you look at it
It makes you more authoritative in a specific field
For example, how to analyze the stock market
Right?
Finance has a lot to say
Both of these represent your own opinions.
They can represent some viewpoints.
You can act as an IP account.
Next, let's talk about common mistakes in choosing a profile picture.
Some students, for instance,
tend to pick accounts they personally like,
Instead of considering the users or followers
accounts that are more favored by the audience.
Here, we prohibit using landscapes or cartoon images.
Anime, right?
Flora and fauna, you know.
Right?
Users can't figure out what your account is about just by looking at your profile picture.
They can't tell what your account is all about.
So it loses the purpose and value of having a profile picture.
Right?
A good profile picture has three criteria, you see.
If it's a personal account, for instance,
Use your personal image as a profile picture
either a photo of yourself or a cartoon version
or an animated style avatar, that works too
and it’s best to incorporate elements related to your profession
like for a corporate account
use the brand logo as the profile picture
combining the logo and the name is also a good option
this helps users recognize
and remember you
Secondly, it needs to align with the overall exhibition design planning.
The third point is that the profile picture should give a comfortable first impression.
It doesn't have to be elaborate.
It doesn't have to be flashy.
But it must be comfortable.
We've already talked about the nickname.
The third point about your profile picture is to write your About section.
Similarly, a great sister also has three criteria.
The first point is to be easy to understand.
It’s clear at first glance
What are you talking about?
The second point is that it’s concise
Your summarizing skills are crucial
A single sentence can provide the recipient with ample information
After all, the About section has a limit on the number of edits you can make.
Right?
The third point is that it’s even more valuable
You need to convey something to the user
What value can you bring to the user?
This way, he will have the motivation to follow.
Right?
To know yourself and your opponent,
you need to look at these aspects of your competitors.
Take a look at them often.
Those benchmark accounts we found earlier, right?
The character settings of ten benchmark accounts,
Their initial video works
the style
the content, and so on
we should start by imitating
on TikTok, never create anything on your own
start by imitating
you need to watch and observe a lot
but the content should still be original
You should go and give it to your followers.
and offer value to your users
Let's talk about this.
The third part is about the comparison.
The crucial aspect is Douyin's traffic distribution algorithm.
Before we dive into the algorithm,
let's take a look at the traffic entry points on Douyin.
In this diagram,
It's actually the source of traffic for this live stream.
Actually, it's the same for our short videos.
We can see the entry with the highest traffic recommendation.
This is what we call the fade flow, right?
The same goes for short videos.
What exactly is the fade flow?
It's when you're scrolling through short videos
you keep swiping through the feed non-stop,
moving up and down continuously.
This is known as the fade flow.
And it includes other similar features,
So many tabs to follow
Others, searching for personal profiles
and also include paid traffic
all of these are your traffic entry points
What we focus on primarily
The biggest thing is the traffic for the For You recommendations, right?
So when we talk about the recommended traffic
we need to understand a concept
the concept of a traffic pool
When we manage Douyin accounts
When it comes to short videos,
there's a concept of a traffic pool.
It categorizes accounts into different tiers,
or you could say influencers, right?
These are divided into different traffic pools.
Or, more commonly, they are categorized by the content itself.
Because each piece of content is relatively independent.
However, different accounts have different weights.
Right?
So, its initial traffic is different from the start
So, for those with not many followers,
Or those with lower weight
They all receive a cold start traffic
No matter what content you post
You'll be given an initial traffic pool to test your content
To evaluate the performance of your content
The initial traffic pool is roughly between 200 to 500
If your content performs well within 200 to 500
It performs better in terms of views compared to other works.
Especially when it comes to works in your field.
Then it will move to the next traffic pool.
This is known as the thousand-person traffic pool.
Each time you win a match, right?
It will be promoted to the next traffic pool.
It will eventually be pushed to your trending traffic pool
It's great.
This is what it means to go viral.
Between 500 and 1,000
10 million views
Ultimately, it will be used for the site-wide recommendations.
Our mechanism, in the context of Douyin
Is known as the horse-race mechanism
Right?
Although it's quite harsh
It's relatively fair, isn't it?
The basic algorithm for account weight on Douyin is
So how do we go about it?
To judge the quality of your account,
we'll look at the following factors,
a few metrics and algorithms.
One is the data dimension,
the quality of the content itself,
and the second is the techniques used in posting content,
For example, you might participate in some trending challenges.
adding relevant hashtags.
Local location and so on
It's about riding the wave of trending topics
Jumping on trends counts too
The third point is the interaction data of your content
This is the best reflection of our content quality
One data metric is the completion rate
like rate
comment
Share and follow
The most crucial thing is the completion rate.
Because, including Douyin,
Others are the same as other short video platforms.
what value can you provide to the platform?
you can keep people around,
first, you can keep people on the platform,
so the completion rate,
is quite important for the platform's evaluation,
any other trending tags
Trending music and so on
can also be considered
as four techniques to boost the play count of your content
So I'd like to share this with everyone.
to improve our completion rates
we often hear about working on data
which means improving these key metrics
The second point is to encourage new users to like the content.
Increase this like count
The third point is to get users to share.
Boost your comment shares
The fourth point is to boost user recognition.
This will naturally increase the shares.
So, how can we make good use of Douyin's recommendation algorithm?
Here are two key points to consider.
One is to adjust the release time of our content.
According to our statistics,
62% of users are on Douyin
these Douyin users
or they browse Douyin before meals and before bed
or while commuting to work or using the restroom
and other fragmented moments
only 10% browse Douyin
so the best time to post content
although there isn't a standard rule
refers to weekdays
At noon at 12, and in the afternoon at 4 and 6 o'clock.
And from 8 to 10 in the evening.
Or on Friday evenings and weekends, and so on.
All of these times,
are just when people might be more free, that's all.
At most, they can serve as a reference.
But the truly scientific timing for posting,
we need to analyze ourselves.
We need to predict what happens after you post.
At which point in time were your target users at that time
Is this the best state to watch this video?
right
for example, let's take a look at a case
like this kind of motivational content
motivational or emotional content
from 8 PM to 11 PM
it's more suitable for posting
because the majority of men and women in this group
Or it's the prime time when people feel particularly lonely and empty.
You know?
Posting this kind of content now perfectly aligns with that.
Right?
And motivational or career-related content,
the best times are from 8 to 9 AM and from 11 to 12 PM.
That's their golden hour, isn't it?
The second tip is to improve our engagement.
These four indicators are aimed at increasing our likes.
number of comments
the number of shares, and the article broadcast rate, these four metrics
So, if you want to get featured on For You
The first thing you need to do is include it in your video description.
We need to guide users to like and comment.
the action of forwarding or finishing watching a video
For example, we can guide users in this comment section.
Go and give it a like
Follow
We often scroll through videos
Check out if the comment section of others also has such guidance.
We can also include descriptions for short videos.
or at the beginning or end of the video
with phrases like 'make sure to watch until the end' and so on
right?
using a bit of these tactics
The third point is in the video description.
Set up some interactive questions
Guide users to leave comments
Boost the number of comments
The fourth tip is to join some challenges
Ways to get trending with challenges
like riding the wave of current hot topics, right?
So, we can do this by
We can learn from this
and later, we can interact in the student group
Go ahead and like and comment on each other's posts.
Let's go over this basic data.
Alright, for the fourth part, we'll cover this topic.
This is...
When it comes to account management,
the most crucial part is content creation.
While we manage accounts,
we rely on the content, right?
Let's first take a look at
what kind of content tends to gain more traction.
So, I've summarized four points for you.
One is to be emotionally genuine.
To have courage,
and to be principled and sincere.
This aligns well with Douyin's values, right?
The second point is to be entertaining.
To have a sense of fun.
Your video has its own appeal to attract users.
Compared to other videos
For example, something mundane
Videos like this in your social circle
needs to stand out
The third point is to have a good amount of content
So you can include some valuable information
with practical use
that others can learn from
For instance, you can teach people something like this
For example, if you run a weight loss account
You can teach others methods to lose weight
Right?
For example, if you specialize in food
You can teach everyone how to make these recipes
So this is a content sharing segment.
The fourth one is about oil
The video I'm referring to
Can have a strong stance
With depth
Have your own perspective
That's like building a persona of an opinion leader
Right?
I'll share a few tips to help you get trending.
On Douyin, for instance
Before we create this content
We can jump on the bandwagon of trending topics
Like the hot trends on Douyin
The trending list
And you can align it with trending topics, right?
The content used in trending topics,
like music or text,
right?
We can mimic it, can't we?
For example, the video network of Douyin.
on our profiles,
the popularity chart,
and the music chart, and so on.
We can use this one from the music chart as the background music.
Right?
And also, consider the location.
For example, the ones that are currently trending.
Because some of them might be regional.
So, set your location to here.
Or change your city setting to this place.
There’s a good chance it will help.
It could be quite beneficial.
The last point is about what we call paid traffic.
That is Doujia.
We can invest in promoting your work.
Invest in Doujia.
Of course.
Why is it considered an embellishment?
It’s an action that adds to the beauty of something already good.
Because if the groundwork isn’t solid,
If your content isn’t good,
So, this influencer isn't very useful for you.
Because even if it was recommended to you with this traffic
you still can't convert it, right?
It doesn't really help much.
But the influencer,
their main role is to help you,
break through the initial traffic pool, right?
For example, your content is really good,
but you're a new account, after all.
Or, I guess your account's weight is relatively low, right?
But, it's due to its own limitations, isn't it?
So, at this point, Douyin can
help you quickly break through this traffic level.
OK, let's take a look at another high-quality piece.
It must meet the following conditions.
First and foremost,
we need to ensure we comply with the rules,
adhering to the platform's regulations.
You need to understand some of the algorithms of this machine.
For example, his recommendation algorithm
And the algorithms used for content review.
The review mechanisms and so on.
The second point is that we need to leverage.
Leverage the user's perspective to assist us.
We need to grasp what the user really wants.
You need to understand what aspects of content the user is interested in.
So, we should try to highlight these points upfront.
When we talk about introducing short videos, we're aiming for gold.
The first three seconds are platinum, right?
A golden second, platinum three seconds, got it?
Most importantly, we need to create short videos.
As long as you have a sense of the internet.
You need to understand the rhythm and other aspects of these short videos.
You should try to imitate them.
Because of his video
Overall, they are due to his script.
There is this formula
Including various representations by others
Expression techniques
For example, the plot
If you're doing a story-based one
You need to work on the storyboards
If you're going for a live-action appearance
Then the actor's expressions, mannerisms, movements, and lines
All need to be optimized
When creating content, you need to choose the right topic, right?
First and foremost, you need to select a topic.
The topic we choose will determine the direction of our work.
It will define the main theme and message of the piece.
Now, when it comes to writing titles and copy,
what are the common strategies for choosing topics?
Here, I've summarized a few key points for you.
The first one is the suspense approach.
Whether it's the content of this video or the posts, they are all good.
It piques the audience's curiosity
It draws the audience in
At this point, they tend to pause and stay, right?
This gives them a reason to keep watching
At this point, your user engagement time
Will naturally increase
The second approach is the questioning method
We can go ahead and trigger this user's comment.
Which sparks user debate
He might leave a nasty comment about you
Right?
Although he insults you
But he will bring you a lot of comments.
So at this point, wouldn't your data improve as well?
For example, we can
Using rhetorical questions or interrogative sentences, right?
For instance, let's take an example
our top-ranked Three Kingdoms general
It turned out not to be Lü Bu
Using this kind of rhetorical question
There will definitely be people who come to argue with you, right?
That's when your comment finally shows up, doesn't it?
The third point is about practicality
Mm-hmm, this can prompt users to favorite.
And they'll want to put it into practice
They can try it out themselves
This is particularly suitable for content that's informative and practical
Or tips and tricks.
We can guide users to like and favorite.
Let me share another trick with you all.
For example, if you want to share something
or a recipe or something similar,
you can create an image to place in the middle.
But make sure it doesn't flash by too quickly.
Because if it flashes by in just a second,
they definitely won't be able to see it clearly.
Right?
If it's not clear, will it pause?
We can come back and replay it.
We might have to watch it multiple times.
At this point, your view rate,
won't the dwell time increase?
Let's make sure we cover the discussion topics.
The most important thing is to include knowledge or valuable content,
something substantial.
The key is to give users a sense of gain.
Then make the user feel like they've enjoyed watching your video
They shouldn’t feel like they wasted their time.
Let's summarize what we've discussed.
To sum up, the most important point is:
We need to evoke emotions in users,
whether it's joy,
sadness,
or anger, and so on.
Once this emotion is present,
your spread and growth will follow.
Now, let's take another look.
Many students say my work
why when they post them,
they only get a few hundred or even just a few dozen views,
which is quite disappointing.
What could be the reasons for it not being recommended?
You need to check these points to see if you've covered them.
For example, does it have any watermarks?
For example, did you reference someone else's materials?
Did you remove the watermarks?
Then,
The second point to check is
whether there's any inappropriate content.
TikTok really emphasizes this.
the health education of minors,
whether there's any borderline content.
Go check it yourself
And there’s this suspected ad content
Talking about this video of yours,
It has too much ad content
Or the ads are too blatant
Right?
The purpose of creating content on Douyin or any platform
Is definitely to drive traffic
So ads are inevitable, right?'
But you can't say this ten-second video
eight or nine seconds are all ads
So, we need to create this kind of soft ad
and maybe at the end
one to two seconds guiding the viewer is enough
Also, you should take a look yourself
at the type of content you post on your account
if it's consistently of lower quality
and monotonous
Then, whenever the recommendations aren't effective,
it will gradually reduce the account's weight.
And the quality of your video is just too poor.
it’s very blurry,
making it impossible for people to understand what you're trying to convey.
Alright, for the fifth section, let's talk about a few operational tips.
Let’s discuss some operational techniques.
Previously, we talked about creating content, right?
So when we create content,
We need some materials or resources
Because a lot of things
We can't just create out of thin air
Or generate on our own
Since we're managing these accounts
Our positioning for ourselves
Is more as content producers
Rather than content creators, right?
Given that we're producing
We can take inspiration from others,
from third-party platforms or other platforms,
content created by other authors, right?
We can adapt and recreate that content.
Here, I'd like to recommend a few platforms to you.
First, I'd like to recommend Sina Weibo to everyone.
Because many of the trending topics on Douyin,
their information lags behind Sina Weibo.
Generally, once something trends on Weibo,
He only gets to catch these trends on Douyin.
So, a lot of our content or creative inspiration
can be found on Weibo, yeah.
There are also other third-party news platforms.
For example, today's headlines and other news platforms.
News-related ones.
We can take these trending topics and use them,
to create secondary content,
or combine these topics to catch the latest trends.
Is that right?
There are other unique aspects as well.
The content from official accounts is also good.
Because there are quite a few high-quality ones.
Official accounts also tend to capitalize on trending topics.
I believe it was recently, in the past period.
The popularity of Dong Yuhui and Oriental Selection.
It was all over the internet.
No matter which platform you open.
It's mostly them.
It's all about Dong Yongheng and Oriental Selection, and so on.
And some from Luo Yonghao as well.
So everyone is jumping on the bandwagon.
Right?
You can do the same.
Isn't that right?
Apart from what I mentioned earlier,
You can also take inspiration from others.
some video platforms both domestically and internationally
such as TikTok and YouTube
And domestic platforms like Watermelon Video and Bilibili, among others.
you can also visit
Take a look at the content of their videos.
and then create your own content
of course, when we talk about drawing inspiration
we don’t mean directly copying or stealing content
the second tip is about how many posts to release daily
This piece works well in this setting.
We need to choose based on our own positioning.
If you're into matrix-style operations,
you need to post a lot, right?
Because the production and maintenance costs of your video are relatively low.
We're doing this kind of short video for product promotion.
Or, creating such posts for product promotion is also good, right?
you don't really care about the number of views, right?
We just rely on luck, right?
Increase his chances
Then we can send out a lot
But each account should not exceed ten posts per day
If you're going for the premium route, right?
I want to focus on operating one account well
Gradually build up this account
At this point, it wouldn't be suitable to post in bulk
You might post three to five times a week
to the carefully crafted video
That's already pretty good.
The third point is to enhance our presence on Douyin.
This involves increasing the visibility of your account.
As mentioned earlier, complete your profile thoroughly.
We've already covered that, right?
The more detailed your bio, the better.
And try to avoid including any advertising elements in it.
For example, don't post things like
your WeChat ID.
The user experience of your followers
When the follower account has a lower weight,
There aren't many followers.
The second one is your work
like it must be original
so there's no need to elaborate on that
if it's not original, right
you won't pass their review
even if we do want to take some inspiration
you should still clean up the content you borrow
at least make the algorithm think it's original, right
Um, reuploading is like the video you're reuploading.
You need to take action.
It's about participating in water transport activities.
Participating in this can even allow you to join the challenge, right?
Nowadays, we often scroll through videos.
there's a 'Join Challenge' button in the top left corner, right?
Go ahead and take on the challenge.
Draw inspiration from popular topics.
Like dangerous information and such.
Dangerous information.
Things everyone understands, like value-added services,
or those that violate advertising regulations,
stuff like that.
It's best to stay away from legal issues.
Another point is to avoid being limited on Douyin,
Don't get yourself into this Penalty Zone
While they often give you a heads up,
telling you which part of your account is in violation,
We can check through the settings.
Often, he won't remind you.
At such times, we should try to avoid it.
This helps prevent frequent signaling of the account.
Please do not use this emulator.
For example, as we mentioned before when registering accounts,
using one phone to register multiple accounts, and so on.
Also, logging in with multiple accounts on the same Wi-Fi.
These actions are likely to be flagged by the platform.
They might consider you a marketing account.
Or working on this marketing team, right?
If one account has an issue,
the other accounts will also be affected.
The sixth point we'll cover is
how to drive traffic and monetize on Douyin.
We mentioned that
the methods of monetization,
such as live streaming sales, right?
like directly linking to the mini shopping cart, there are several ways to promote.
One way is through the TikTok showcase.
Open a TikTok showcase.
Another way is to open your own TikTok store.
Become a TikTok merchant.
There are some differences between them.
The permissions vary.
Let's start with the personal account setup.
How to open a product showcase.
There are a few conditions to meet first.
For personal verification, you need to post over ten works.
Your Douyin account has around 1,000 followers who have completed real-name verification.
Finally, pay a 500 yuan deposit to activate it.
For personal zero-follower activation,
Douyin currently has some flexibility,
there are some relaxations in live streaming sales,
but this is only for certain accounts,
specifically for some older and newer accounts,
which have the privilege of zero-follower activation.
So, the same goes for real-name verification, right?
A deposit is also required, of course.
Another thing is that you need to open this betting shop, right?
You can open a store yourself.
You can do it as an individual.
All you need is a business license for an individual entrepreneur.
Other methods include account authorization, right?
A Douyin store can manage up to five Douyin accounts.
For example, you can use your five employees' Douyin accounts.
You can bind it.
Then you can activate that showcase.
Additionally, if you activate it for a business use,
your showcase will also be activated.
For this, you will need the business’s business license.
Next, let's analyze this further.
Let's reverse-engineer why Douyin is so addictive.
Once we figure this out,
we'll know what makes it tick.
Why do target users enjoy watching our work?
At this point,
you'll know how to proceed with your content.
We need to understand the algorithm behind it.
One aspect of its logic is intelligent distribution,
Another one is the combination of For You recommendations and the addition of popularity groups.
First, let's start.
Let's take a look at the logic of intelligent distribution.
The algorithm of the Toutiao system
It stands out from other internet products
due to its decentralized traffic distribution
For example, traffic on Weibo
is often concentrated around major influencers
New Weibo accounts
tend to have no viewers
But if you create an account on Toutiao
Even if you have zero followers
Any video that is released
His system will smartly distribute content for you
from dozens to hundreds of views
as a starting traffic, right?
And the traffic methods for his new videos are diverse.
Most of them focus on this area and following.
along with user behavior tags
and content tags for smart distribution
If your new video's completion rate is measured,
and a high engagement rate
So, this video of yours
will receive a dose of traffic boost to the next level
which is why it's possible to have zero followers on Douyin
and still gain ten thousand followers overnight
the reason for an overnight sensation
That's why Douyin's decentralized algorithm
allows everyone to get a fair share
which is also why we focus on creating a matrix of accounts for operations
this increases the chances of hitting a viral hit
The most critical aspect is the various weights.
His hot dog posts also need a lot of shares.
higher than your comment and like counts
The weight has to be higher.
So, the video you've posted
how does Douyin review it?
It's roughly divided into these three steps.
First, the algorithm screens and initiates the process.
The traffic value report,
Assuming we upload videos on Douyin every day,
There are one million people uploading these short videos
TikTok, on the other hand, randomly assigns each short video a
cold start traffic pool with average exposure.
For example,
Each short video, once reviewed and approved, is then released.
it gets an average of 1,000 views.
The second step is data screening.
At this point, it would be like selecting from one million short videos.
1,000 views from the 1 million short videos,
to analyze your likes and comments
Follow, share, and other metrics
which is the top 10% quality,
the top 10% of these videos.
the top 10% of these videos
and the top 10% in likes, comments, and shares is selected again.
Let's check out the top 10% for likes, comments, shares, and so on.
round by round, to screen out our content.
It works like this,
Finally, after multiple rounds of screening and testing,
your content will be seen by users,
will then enter this premium For You traffic pool
When users open the app and see videos with hundreds of thousands of likes,
Seeing those videos that rack up millions of likes
On Douyin, some behaviors are likely to violate the platform's rules and guidelines.
One is reposting videos,
like downloading videos and posting them directly.
One is reuploading videos.
For example, you download a video from the cloud.
if your content is too heavily focused on advertising,
all ads, no actual content,
that's definitely not allowed and not favored by the platform.
Negative content is also a no-go.
Douyin's slogan is 'Record a Better Life',
so for every operator,
any negative content should be avoided.
If reported, it will be strictly reviewed.
It's also a feature for the platform to dislike
such as your account nickname,
Douyin handle,
personal bio,
video descriptions, and private messages or comments,
anywhere you can input text on Douyin can be a place for keyword violations.
So, everyone needs to be cautious.
If there are any, they should be deleted promptly.
We will share a list of keywords in the group,
which you can check before posting.
Just review your content accordingly.
Lastly, let's talk about some of Douyin's rules.
Your video description and private comments
we must rely on the platform and follow its rules.
We need to know what the 'Nine Layers of the Demon Tower' on Douyin are.
First, a blurry profile picture or a random nickname,
for Douyin, these indicate a low-quality account,
Then we'll share a link in the group for everyone.
These are things to avoid.
Regarding the keywords we mentioned earlier,
let's look at a few common ones used across platforms,
such as those that violate advertising laws,
which are not allowed on any platform,
like 'first
Here, I'd like to recommend a few